Imogen Cunningham
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Newberry, James H.: Sep 13, 1969
New Directions: Apr 01, 1963*; Jan 22, 1964*
Newhall, Beaumont and Nancy: mentioned in [undated] letter from Cunningham to unidentified correspondent; Aug 26, 1957; Aug 05, 1967*; Aug 09, 1967; Aug 12, 1967*; Jan 24, 1968; Feb 02, 1968*; May 03, 1968*; Sep 17, 1969; Sep 23, 1969; Mar 03, 1971 (including resume for Beaumont Newhall); Mar 09, 1971*; Jul 17, 1974; Jul 24, 1974*; Aug 15, 1974; also see Eastman: George Eastman House; also see Writings
Newman, Arnold: Sep 02, 1969*; Dec 31, 1969; Jan 06, 1970*; Jan 16, 1970*; Apr 17, 1970; Aug 03, 1970*
Newmann, Vera: see Vera
New Orleans Museum of Art: Jun 17, 1974
New Roses (gallery): undated
Newsweek: Sep 03, 1974; Sep 12, 1974*; Apr 04, 1975*
New Yorker: Nov 19, 1962
New York Graphic Society, Ltd.: Sep 25, 1974; Oct 01, 1974*; Oct 16, 1974; Feb 25, 1976; Mar 09, 1976*; Mar 12, 1976
New York Times: May 02, 1973; May 06, 1973*
New York Times Book Review: Oct 31, 1966*; Nov 03, 1966
Nicastro, Peter: see Writings
Nord, Ina: Dec 10, 1950
Nordberg, Rod: Feb 06, 1975; Feb 19, 1975*
Norman, Dorothy: Oct 28, 1959*; Nov 02, 1959; Nov 05, 1959
Norman, Mrs. P.: Oct 08, 1973*; Jun 07, 1974*; Oct 15, 1974*; Nov 21, 1974*
Norris University Center: see Northwestern University
Northwestern University: Apr 22, 1975
Norton: W. W. Norton & Company, Inc. Katherine Barnard): Jan 08, 1957; Jan 18, 1957*; Jan 21, 1957; Feb 02, 1957*
Noskowiak, Sonya: Jan 08, 1974*; Dec 25, 1974
Novack, Ellen: Aug 27, 1967; Apr 22, 1973
Noyes, Pat and Dick: Feb 06, 1966*; Jan 25, 1967; Feb 06, 1967*; Jul 31, 1967*; Sep 26, 1967*; Oct 12, 1967; Oct 29, 1967*; Jun 02, 1968; Sep 13, 1968*; Jan 04, 1969*; Jan 11, 1969; Apr 28, 1969; Jul 15, 1969; Jul 25, 1969*; Dec 12, 1969*; Dec 29, 1969*; May 16, 1970; Jan 24, 1971; Apr 01, 1971*; Nov 16, 1971*; May 24, 1972; Jun 08, 1972*; [May 1973] (including a photograph of a mountain range; Oct 24, 1973; Nov 30, 1973*; [Dec 02, 1973]; Dec 02, 1974; Jan 27, 1975*; Jul 22, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Oakland Art Museum: Mar 11, 1963; Mar 14, 1963*; Mar 19, 1963; Jul 07, 1967; Oct 14, 1968; Dec 27, 1973; Mar 11, 1974; Mar 28, 1974; Aug 27, 1974; Oct 23, 1974; Jan 08, 1974; Jan 16, 1975*; Jan 22, 1975*; Feb 25, 1975; Mar 18, 1975; Apr 14, 1976; Jun 03, 1976; also see Heyman, Therese
Oakland Museum Association: Dec 20, 1965; Apr 25, 1969
Oakland Public Museum: Nov 15, 1957; Nov 25, 1957; May 17, 1971
Oka, Jane: Jun 30, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
O'Keeffe, Georgia: undated Christmas card; Feb 08, 1971*; Feb 16, 1971; May 02, 1971; Jan 31, 1972; Feb 04, 1974*; Feb 11, 1974; Jan 31, 1975; Mar 16, 1976; Mar 24, 1976*; Apr 02, 1976
Oklahoma: University of Oklahoma Press: Dec 16, 1957; Jan 03, 1958*; Jan 24, 1958; Jan 17, 1958*; Jan 31, 1958; Feb 25, 1958; Mar 07, 1958*
Olsen, Cynthia: Sep 29, 1970; Oct 24, 1970*
Oregon: University of Oregon: Sep 23, 1965; Feb 23, 1966; Feb 28, 1966*; Mar 07, 1966; Apr 11, 1966; Apr 12, 1966*; Nov 16, 1966; Nov 25, 1966*; Dec 14, 1966; Feb 03, 1967; Feb 06, 1967*; Feb 20, 1967; [Mar 1967]; Apr 17, 1967; Apr 24, 1967; May 01, 1967; May 25, 1967; Jun 21, 1967*; Jun 23, 1967; Jul 27, 1967; Jul 28, 1967*; Aug 02, 1967*; Aug 31, 1967; Sep 05, 1967; Sep 06, 1967; Sep 17, 1967*; Sep 26, 1967; Oct 06, 1967*; Oct 07, 1967*; Oct 11, 1967; Oct 13, 1967*; Apr 09, 1968; Apr 17, 1968*; Apr 19, 1968*; May 17, 1968; Mar 16, 1969; Mar 30, 1969*; Apr 25, 1973; Nov 16, 1974; Dec 02, 1974*
Orion Service & Trading Co., Inc.: Aug 08, 1958; Aug 17, 1958*
Orpet, Mildred: Feb 03, 1958; Feb 06, 1958*
Oskar, Keri: Sep 14, 1972; Sep 19, 1972*
Ostroff, Eugene: see Smithsonian Institution
Otis, Norman: Apr 08, 1949
Outerbridge & Dienstfrey: Mar 10, 1972
Owings, Margaret Wentworth: undated (4)
Ozenfant, Amedee: Oct 05, 1939; Nov 25, 1939; [1940]; Feb 26, 1940
P., J.: Feb 26, 1975
Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company: Jan 16, 1952; Jan 20, 1952*; Oct 29, 1968*; Nov 07, 1968; May 01, 1969*
, Christina: Dec 12, 1950 (typescript of "A Passion for the Medium" by for Modern Photography)
Palfi, Marion: Apr 13, 1976
Palmer, Jon: undated
Palmer, Phil: Dec 01, 1965
Parasol Press: Jan 15, 1974*
Park, David: mentioned in letter dated Dec 26, 1961 from United States Information Agency
Park, Henry (Susan Park's son): May 10, 1970; Dec 07, 1972
Park, Susan: May 05, [1968]; Oct 31, 1968; Jul 24, 1969*; Aug 21, 1969*; Nov 21, 1969*; Nov 30, 1969; Dec 06, 1969*; Jan 03, 1972; Dec 07, 1972; Jan 17, 1973*; Dec 04, 1973
Parker, Elizabeth: May 20, 1960 (including a Cunningham photograph of Parker, circa 1906)
Parker, Fred: see Pasadena Art Museum
Parkin, John: May 08, 1974*; Apr 08, 1976; Jul 14, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Parrish, Martha Cunningham: Feb 15, 1968; Jul 19, 1968*
Partridge, Bruce: Jun 07, 1966; Jan 03, 1974
Partridge, Gryffyd, Janet, Rym, and Loren: undated (3); Mar 30, 1943; Sep 03, 1943*; [1944]; Jul 14, 1946*; Feb 28, 1954; Jun 19, 1958; Nov 05, 1958*; Nov 05, 1958 (2); Oct 11, 1959*; Apr 14, 1960*; Apr 18, 1960; Apr 18, 1960; Apr 21, 1960*; Apr 30, 1960*; May 08, 1960*; May 18, 1960*; May 26, 1960; May 28, 1960*; Jun 04, 1960*; Jun 07, 1960*; Aug 03, 1960 (letter to Henry Gallery); Aug 05, 1960*; Feb 27, 1961; Apr 03, 1961; Jun 22, 1961; Aug 31, 1961; Sep 05, 1961; Sep 09, 1961*; Sep 13, 1961; Sep 18, 1961; Sep 21, 1961; Sep 29, 1961; Oct 08, 1961; Oct 19, 1961; Nov 10, 1961; Nov 13, 1961; Nov 21, 1961; Nov 27, 1961; Nov 27, 1961*; Dec 01, 1961; Jan 01, 1962; Apr 18, 1963*; Mar 12, 1965*; Apr 18, 1965*; Nov 27, 1966 (announcement of Loren's wedding to Frank Tose); Apr 19, 1967; Jun 01, 1968*; Jun 27, 1968*; Jul 04, 1968*; Jul 05, 1968; Jul 11, 1968*; Jul 22, 1968; Jul 27, 1968*; Aug 07, 1968*; Aug 09, 1968*; Aug 11, 1968*; Jan 24, 1970*; Nov 21, 1970 (2); Jun 21, 1971*; Aug 19, 1971; Feb 03, 1973*; Apr 30, 1974 (letter from Padraic); Jun 24, 1974 (letter from Dorothy MacDonald); Aug 21, 1974 (letter from Cunningham's lawyers, Morrison, Foerster, Holloway, Clinton & Clark); Aug 27, 1974; Sep 20, 1974; Feb 18, 1975 (letter from Cunningham's lawyers, Morrison & Foerster); also see Partridge, Loren
Partridge, Loren: Oct 04, 1968*; Oct 05, 1968; Oct 11, 1968*; Oct 17, 1968; Oct 31, 1968*; Nov 12, 1968*; Nov 21, 1968*; Dec 05, 1968*; Dec 08, 1968; Dec 14, 1968*; Jan 25, 1969*; Mar 03, 1969*; May 03, 1969*; Jun 04, 1969*; Jun 16, 1969*; Jun 21, 1969; Jul 19, 1969; Jul 22, 1969*; Jul 23, 1969*; Aug 09, 1969; Aug 09, 1969*; Sep 03, 1969; Oct 08, 1969*; Aug 02, 1971; Jan 27, 1974*; Feb 25, 1974*
Partridge, Padraic, Marjorie, and Kayla: undated (27); Aug 24, 1942; Sep 14, 1942; Jun 12, 1947; Sep 10, 1947; Nov 03, 1947; Dec 18, 1947; Jan 16, 1950; Sep 11, 1951 (Kayla's birth announcement); Jun 24, 1960; Sep 16, 1960; Jan 14, 1961*; May 09, 1961; Jan 10, 1962; May 20, 1962*; Jun 09, 1962*; Jul 23, 1962; Sep 10, 1962*; Dec 31, 1962; Sep 05, 1964*; Jan 18, 1965*; Mar 07, 1965*; Mar 25, 1965 (including 4 poems by Kayla); Apr 18, 1965* (2); Aug 11, 1965*; Aug 11, 1965; Aug 14, 1965*; Jan 12, 1966*; Feb 01, 1966*; May 08, 1966*; Aug 07, 1966; Aug 10, 1966*; Oct 04, 1966*; Nov 13, 1966*; Dec 1966; Dec 05, 1966*; Jan 04, 1967*; May 18, 1967; May 22, 1967*; Sep 22, 1967*; Oct 04, 1967*; Dec 03, 1967*; Feb 14, 1968*; Apr 10, 1968*; May 23, 1968*; Jul 07, 1968*; Sep 27, 1968*; Nov 30, 1968*; Jan 15, 1969; Mar 12, 1969*; Jul 23, 1969*; Dec 12, 1969*; Apr 01, 1972; Jan 11, 1973; Jan 12, 1974*; Jan 23, 1974; Jan 24, 1974*; Jan 26, 1974; Jan 29, 1974; Jan 31, 1974*; Feb 12, 1974*; Mar 08, 1974*; Apr 05, 1974*; Apr 16, 1974*; Apr 30, 1974 (letter to Gryffyd); May 12, 1974; May 27, 1974*; Jun 08, 1974*; Aug 13, 1974*; [Sep 11], 1974; Sep 14, 1974*; Sep 15, 1974*; Sep 28, 1974; Oct 02, 1974*; Nov 07, 1974; Nov 07, 1974; Dec 01, 1974*; Dec 24, 1974*; Dec 26, 1974*; Dec 27, 1974*; Feb 22, 1975*; Feb 28, 1975*; Mar 17, 1975; also see Photographs
Partridge, Roi and May Ellen: undated (6); Jun 16, 1958; Sep 13, 1958; Nov 07, 1958; Nov 12, 1958; Apr 15, 1960*; Dec 16, 1961; Sep 01, 1964; Mar 03, 1965; Apr 07, 1967; Apr 22, 1967; Apr 24, 1967*; Jan 06, 1968*; Apr 12, 1968; May 23, 1968; Nov 29, 1968*; Dec 27, 1968; Jul 23, 1969; Aug 12, 1969*; Aug 19, 1970; Dec 22, 1971*; Apr 1972 (poem to Rym); Sep 21, 1973; May 09, 1974; May 22, 1974*; May 22, 1974* (2); Apr 05, 1975; Jan 01, 1976; Jan 21, 1976; Feb 10, 1976; Feb 14, 1976; Apr 19, 1976; Jun 30, 1976 (letter to Gryffyd Partridge)
Partridge, Rondal, Elizabeth, Joan, Joshua, Aaron, Betsy, and Meg: undated (5); Jul 07, 1940; Sep 27, 1953*; Jan 04, 1959; Jan 03, 1960; Jul 24, 1960; Oct 14, 1961; Dec 17, 1961; Sep 29, 1962; Dec 26, 1962; Feb 08, 1965*; Apr 08, 1965*; May 04, 1965*; Apr 18, 1965*; May 10, 1965; Jun 07, 1965*; Jun 20, 1965*; Jul 03, 1965; Jul 07, 1965*; Jul 08, 1965*; Aug 04, 1965*; Aug 26, 1967 (announcement of Joan's wedding to Bruce Haynes); Jul 14, 1968*; Jul 31, 1968*; Aug 23, 1968*; Oct 14, 1968*; Dec 29, 1973; Jan 17, 1974*; Nov 29, 1974*
Pasadena Art Museum: Sep 29, 1969; Nov 19, 1969*; Oct 20, 1970; May 14, 1974
Pascal, Naomi: undated
Patkowska, Marja (Maryla): Nov 06, 1963; Sep 10, 1964; Sep 11, 1965*; Sep 25, 1965; Aug 06, 1967*; Dec 08, 1968*; Feb 08, 1973*Feb 10, 1973*
Pattee, Hilary: Oct 03, 1967; Oct 10, 1967*; Feb 02, 1968
Penick: S. B.Penick & Company (botanical products): Jul 14, 1950
Penington, Ruth: undated; Apr 04, 1974*; May 18, 1974*; May 22, 1974; May 28, 1974*; Apr 02, 1975*; Jun 10, 1975*; Aug 05, 1975 (2)
Percival, Willa: Sep 05, 1968; Feb 09, 1969*
Perry, Mrs.: May 04, 1957*
Phillips, Michael: May 25, 1972*
Phoenix College: Aug 10, 1969; Aug 28, 1969*; Sep 11, 1969; Dec 02, 1969; Dec 09, 1969*; Apr 04, 1975*
Photographer's Gallery: Nov 28, 1973*; May 22, 1974; May 29, 1974*
Photographer's Place: [Mar 31,] 1976
Photographic Society of China: Nov 27, 1962
Photography: Mar 29, 1954; Jan 31, 1955; Feb 15, 1955*; Apr 30, 1955*; Aug 30, 1955; Oct 06, 1955; Feb 02, 1956*; Oct 13, 1957*; Oct 17, 1957; Nov 12, 1958*; Jan 28, 1959*; Feb 03, 1959; Apr 29, 1959; Oct 21, 1959*; Nov 24, 1959*; Jan 01, 1960*; Feb 19, 1960; Oct 16, 1960; Feb 03, 1961; Mar 10, 1961*; Mar 24, 1961*; Apr 07, 1961; May 05, 1961*; May 09, 1961*; Oct 17, 1961; May 04, 1962; Jul 20, 1962; Aug 01, 1962; Aug 10, 1962*; Oct 07, 1962*; Jun 04, 1963; Jun 07, 1963*; May 10, 1965*
Photography Annual: Feb 12, 1954; [Nov 1955] (2); Apr 12, 1956*
Photography House: Jun 21, 1972
Photography in the Fine Arts: Apr 03, 1961; Feb 08, 1963*; Jun 21, 1966; Jun 22, 1966*; Jul 07, 1966; Jul 08, 1966*; Jul 12, 1966*; Jul 26, 1966; Oct 19, 1966 (2); Oct 28, 1966; Nov 04, 1966; Nov 09, 1966*; Dec 09, 1966; Dec 12, 1966*
Photography of the World: Oct 30, 1956
Photography Publishing Corp.: Sep 16, 1953
Photography Year Book: see Photography
Piaskowski, Nata: Jul 14, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Pi Beta Phi Fraternity: undated; May 03, 1961; Nov 28, 1969*; Apr 05, 1970; May 1970; May 30, 1973; May 17, 1974*; Mar 18, 1991
Polaroid Corporation: Mar 09, 1965*; Feb 03, 1966*; May 01, 1973; May 04, 1973*
Polish Embassy: Mar 03, 1961*
Pond-Smith, David: Oct 26, 1974
Poon, Irene: mentioned in letter dated Dec 07, 1968; May 03, 1976; May 04, 1976*
Porter, Allan: see Camera
Porter, Bern: undated (2); May 24, 1960; Feb 05, 1964*
Posner, Irina: May 20, 1976
Powell, Jim: Feb 14, 1975
Prism: Apr 12, 1974
Professional Photographers of Northern California, Inc.: Dec 18, 1962; Jan 04, 1963*
Protze, Jens: Jun 06, 1972*
Publications Photo-Cinema Paul Montel: Nov 07, 1962 (in French)
Purcell, Victor: Dec 29, 1960; Jan 31, 1961*; Feb 28, 1961; Jun 04, 1961
Pynchon, Peter: [Sep 1965]; Apr 11, 1966
Quaker, Anna: Jul 07, 1959*
Quivira Bookshop and Photograph Gallery: Mar 28, 1972
R., Rossi: Feb 12, 1948
Raab, Michael: Jul 21, 1966; Mar 05, 1969*; Apr 07, 1970
Rack, Grace: Oct 11, 1974*
Radin, Rhea: Jun 17, 1976
Rado, Charles: see Guillumette: Paul Guillumette, Inc.
Raffner, Jim: [Dec 1973]*
Rags: Jul 17, 1970*; Aug 11, 1970*; Aug 24, 1970; Aug 27, 1970*
Ramsing, Roy: Aug 17, 1969
Randlett, Mary: Feb 18, 1971; Feb 27, 1971*
Random House, Inc.: Feb 01, 1971; Feb 15, 1971*; Jan 18, 1972; Jan 21, 1972*; Apr 15, 1976; Apr 17, 1976*
Rasmussen, Karen, Margarete, and Steendeiler?: [Dec 1960]; Mar 30, 1961*; Dec 25, 1961; Feb 07, 1966*
Ratcliffe, M. S.: Jan 01, 1973
Ray, Man: mentioned in letter dated Oct 17, 1961; Jan 12, 1969*
Reed, Gervais: see Henry Gallery
Reed, Robert: Oct 31, 1967
Reese, Lynn: [Dec 31, 1971]; Jul 22, 1974; also see Writings
Reimers, Margaret (Peggy): Feb 01, 1965*; Jan 13, 1969*; Mar 16, 1974*
Reynard, Jessica: Jan 27, 1967; Feb 15, 1967*
Reynoso, Louise: Jun 02, 1966*; Feb 16, 1967
Rhodes, Daniel: Jul 09, 1968*; [Jan 1969]; Jun 15, 1970; Aug 04, 1970*; Jun 09, 1971*
Richmond Art Center: Feb 10, 1967
Riordan, Dan: Sep 18, 1962 (including a calling card and a photograph of a stunt rider and horse)
Rioux, Seggei John: May 21, 1975*
Rivera, Diego: mentioned in letter dated Feb 22, 1931
Roberts, Jackie Paul: Jun 19, [1962]; Jul 01, 1962*
Robertson, Clark: Nov 06, 1967; Dec 28, 1969*
Rochester Institute of Technology: Jan 09, 1970; Feb 18, 1970*
Rockford College: Mar 15, 1967
Roerich: Nicholas Roerich Museum: Feb 24, 1960
Roethke, Beatrice and Theodore: Aug 22, 1959; Oct 29, 1959*; Nov 03, 1959 (recommendation to Guggenheim for Cunningham from Theodore Roethke); Nov 11, 1959; Dec 08, 1961; mentioned in letter dated Sep 15, 1965; Oct 21, 1968; Oct 30, 1968*; Jun 11, 1970 (letter to James McLeod); Sep 12, 1971; [Sep 12, 1971]*; May 05, 1972*; May 17, 1972; Oct 14, 1972
Ronis, N.: Feb 15, 1971*
Rosenfeld, Dr.: Sep 04, 1952*
Rosenstein, Mrs.: Jul 23, 1971*
Rosenthal, Ellen: Feb 04, 1971; Sep 12, 1973*; Sep 19, 1973
Ross, Don and Estelle: Oct 08, 1968; Jun 08, 1970; Aug 03, 1970*; Sep 03, 1970; Sep 09, 1970
Ross, Nancy: Apr 08, 1976
Ross, Richard M.: Nov 19, 1968; Nov 22, 1968*; Jan 30, 1969; Feb 18, 1969
Rothstein, Arthur: Mar 12, 1972*
Rowan, Dick: Nov 19, 1970 (5 photographs of Cunningham)
Rubinstein, Eva: Sep 23, 1974; Sep 30, 1974*; Oct 19, 1974*
Rudzinski, Jim: [Jul 1972]
Ruffner, Jim: Apr 09, 1972
Rusk, Virginia Foisie: Jan 06, 1969*; Dec 02, 1971*
Russell, Elizabeth H.: Sep 08, 1954
Rustin, Arnold and Jean: Apr 05, 1965; Apr 24, 1965; Apr 28, 1965; May 04, 1965*; Jun 07, 1965*; Jun 16, 1965; Jun 21, 1965*; Aug 09, 1965*; Mar 05, 1967; Mar 09, 1967*; Sep 16, 1967*; Nov 26, 1967*; Feb 17, 1969*; Sep 20, 1970*; Dec 23, 1971*
Rustin, Debbie: undated*; Dec 10, 1961; Apr 22, 1968; Apr 30, 1968*; May 05, 1968; May 25, 1968; May 30, 1968*; Aug 12, 1968; Sep 03, 1968; Sep 10, 1968 (including photograph); Sep 10, 1968*; Sep 17, 1968; Sep 29, 1968*; Oct 28, 1968; Nov 04, 1968; Nov 23, 1968*; Nov 29, 1968; Jan 31, 1969; Feb 03, 1969*; Dec 02, 1970*; Jan 30, 1971; Mar 03, 1971*; Apr 13, 1971; May 11, 1971*; May 10, 1974; Jul 27, 1974
Ryan, Elaine: Nov 22, 1971
S., B.: Aug 23, 1963*; Sep 30, 1963*; Oct 08, 1968*
S., Thomas: Feb 22, 1931
St. Petersburg: Museum of Fine Arts: Apr 07, 1972
Sandahl, Margaret: [May 1965]; May 13, 1965*
Sands, Don: mentioned in letter dated Mar 06, 1969
San Francisco: Art Commission, City and County of San Francisco: Mar 08, 1973; Mar 28, 1973*; Apr 14, 1973; Sep 10, 1973; Sep 12, 1973*
San Francisco Art Institute: Oct 21, 1970; Jun 21, 1971; Jun 24, 1971*; Apr 17, 1973
San Francisco Chronicle: Feb 23, 1965*; Feb 26, 1965*; Nov 20, 1970*; Sep 23, 1971
San Francisco Examiner: Oct 27, 1969; Nov 09, 1969*
San Francisco International Film Festival: Dec 11, 1966*
San Francisco Museum of Art: Jun 18, 1952; Dec 04, 1964; Mar 19, 1965 (letter to John Humphrey from Phil Palmer); Jul 09, 1965; Sep 23, 1969; Feb 25, 1971; Apr 12, 1973; Feb 19, 1975; Apr 15, 1975
San Francisco Psychoanalytic Institute: Apr 14, 1959; Apr 15, 1959*
San Francisco Public Library: Apr 12, 1973; Apr 16, 1973; Feb 20, 1975; Apr 30, 1975
San Francisco State College: Mar 19, 1964; Mar 20, 1964*; Mar 09, 1965*; Apr 09, 1965*; Jan 14, 1969; Jan 28, 1969 (2); Feb 10, 1969; May 14, 1971
San Francisco Women Artists: Apr 13, 1970 (2); Apr 18, 1970*
San Jose State College: Sep 07, 1965; Mar 22, 1967; Mar 29, 1967*; Apr 03, 1967; Jul 03, 1968; Nov 12, 1968; Jun 01, 1971; also see Donoho, David
Santa Barbara Museum of Art: Apr 03, 1972; Aug 24, 1972*; Nov 21, 1972; Jan 09, 1973*; Mar 29, 1973; Apr 26, 1973*; May 07, 1973; Sep 07, 1973*; Nov 06, 1973; Nov 16, 1973*; Nov 27, 1973; Mar 28, 1974*; Apr 03, 1974; May 03, 1974*; Oct 28, 1974*; Nov 18, 1974; Nov 25, 1974
Santa Clara: University of Santa Clara: May 20, 1966; Feb 09, 1971 (including a booklet of clippings about a University of Santa Clara exhibition)
Santa Rosa-Sonoma County Free Public Library: Feb 24, 1971
Saturday Evening Post: May 24, 1962*; Jul 25, 1962*
Savage, Naomi: Sep 03, 1970; Sep 10, 1970*; Dec 06, 1970; Jun 06, 1971*
Sawahata, Alfred: [1943]; Feb 17, 1943; Mar 08, 1943; Apr 07, 1943; Aug 27, 1944; Jan 26, 1945; Feb 21, 1945; Apr 08, 1945; Mar 19, 1946; Dec 27, 1949; Nov 19, 1950*; Jun 27, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Saxton (U.C. Medical School): Jun 07, 1940
Schaefer, Nance: Oct 09, 1973; Oct 29, 1973*
Schaeffer: Rudolph Schaeffer School of Design: Jan 08, 1967; Nov 05, 1974; Jul 06, 1976
Schappert, Liz: Mar 11, 1969*; Jan 07, 1974*
Scherbatsky, Serge and Phoenix: Feb 26, 1969*; Sep 18, 1973; Nov 14, 1973; Oct 19, 1974*; Mar 24, 1975; May 28, 1975*
Schoener, Allon T.: Dec 02, 1955; Dec 07, 1955*; Feb 05, 1956; Feb 15, 1956*; Feb 27, 1956*; Sep 02, 1956; Dec 02, 1956; Dec 09, 1956*; Jan 01, 1957; Jan 30, 1957*; Feb 18, 1957*; Feb 24, 1957; Feb 26, 1957*; Mar 10, 1957; Apr 06, 1957*; May 19, 1957; Jun 18, 1957*; Nov 08, 1957*; Dec 04, 1957; Dec 26, 1957; Jan 07, 1958*; Mar 10, 1958*; Dec 20, 1958*; Oct 03, 1960; Jan 09, 1973*; Feb 03, 1973*; May 02, 1973*; [Dec 25, 1973]; Jan 07, 1975*; Jan 20, 1975
Schoener, Ida and Harry: Jan 06, 1957; Jan 24, 1957*; Oct 03, 1960
Schoener, Jason and Virginia: Dec 08, 1964; Jun 11, 1965*
Schott-Hawks, Susan: Nov 12, 1973
Schultz, Carl: [Apr 05, 1971*]; Apr 05, 1971
Sculthorp, Esther: Apr 05, 1969*
Seagram: Joseph E. Seagram & Sons, Inc.: Jun 06, 1974; Jun 07, 1974*; Jul 11, 1974
Seattle Art Museum: Jun 30, 1957; Jul 16, 1957; Jan 28, 1959*; Feb 02, 1959; Jun 12, 1959 (letter from Gerdes, Montgomery & Miller re photo of Alfred Salmony); Oct 03, 1964; Dec 08, 1970; Dec 23, 1970*; Jan 22, 1971*; Jan 25, 1971; Jan 26, 1971; Jan 28, 1971*; Feb 08, 1971; May 11, 1971; May 14, 1971*; Jul 04, 1971*
Seattle: Office of Public Services: May 06, 1974*
Seaver, Keven: Aug 02, 1974
Seiberling (Steinberg), Dorothy: see Life
Selz, Peter: see California: University of California at Berkeley:
Semanco, Al and Bill Sonnenstahl: Apr 18, 1973
Shad's Gallery (Shedrich Williams, director): Feb 20, 1974*; Oct 12, 1974; [Oct 11, 1974]; Jan 20, 1975*; Mar 19, 1975*
Shaftel, Stanley: Aug 05, 1974
Shapiro, Norman: Oct 17, 1966; Dec 11, 1966*
Shartsis, Arthur: Mar 30, 1975*; Jun 13, 1975*; Aug 19, 1975; Sep 11, 1975; Sep 12, 1975; Sep 22, 1975; Sep 25, 1975; Nov 21, 1975; Jan 20, 1976; Feb 18, 1976; Mar 02, 1976; Mar 29, 1976; Jun 02, 1976
Sheeler, Charles: Feb 17, 1956
Shelton, Sybil: Sep 29, 1973
Shen Yao: Mar 31, 1955; Dec 11, 1955*; Oct 07, 1965*; Oct 12, 1965; May 07, 1968; Jun 12, 1970; Jan 05, 1971; Jun 21, 1971; Jan 26, 1972; Dec 30, 1972*; May 31, 1973; Jun 12, 1973*; Dec 21, 1973*; Mar 07, 1974; Mar 15, 1974*; Nov 15, 1974*; Jan 10, 1975; Jan 13, 1975*; Jul 31, 1975; Feb 23, 1976; Mar 29, 1976; Apr 23, 1976
Siegel, Arthur: undated
Siembab: Carl Siembab Gallery: Jun 10, 1968; Sep 13, 1968; Sep 17, 1968*; Sep 19, 1968; Oct 04, 1968*; Nov 04, 1968*; Nov 18, 1968; Nov 30, 1968*; Dec 27, 1968*; Mar 10, 1969*; Apr 24, 1969*; Apr 24, 1969; Jul 11, 1969*
Silverman, Jan Edward: Oct 23, 1974; Oct 28, 1974*
Sinel, Jo: Jun 25, 1942; Sep 30, 1964*; Jan 08, 1967
Siskind, Aaron: undated (see Siegel, Arthur); Feb 03, 1968*; Feb 26, 1968
Sivertz, Victorian: Oct 14, 1974; Oct 22, 1974*
Slack, Charles: May 18, 1971; May 24, 1971*
Slattery, Paul: Jan 27, 1940
Smit, R. H.: Jul 25, 1971*
Smith, Ethel Sabin: May 20, 1970 (2); Sep 21, 1970*; Jul 30, 1973*; Aug 27, 1973*
Smith, Henry Holmes: Jun 13, 1970; Jul 20, 1970*; Oct 09, 1970; Feb 02, 1971*
Smith, W. Eugene: Apr 13, 1975
Smithsonian Institution: Jul 11, 1968; Jul 23, 1968; Aug 01, 1968*; Aug 12, 1968; Sep 06, 1968; Oct 14, 1968*; Dec 28, 1968*; Jan 05, 1969*; Jan 13, 1969; Jan 13, 1969*; Jan 26, 1969; Feb 03, 1969*; Feb 08, 1969*; Mar 08, 1969*; Jul 14, 1969*; May 18, 1970; Jun 03, 1971*; Jun 09, 1971*; Jul 08, 1971*; May 29, 1974; Sep 05, 1974*; Jul 09, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge); also see Writings; also see Photographs
Snowden, Earl of: Dec 06, 1965 (letter signed by his secretary)
Snyder: Norman Snyder Studios, Inc.: Mar 04, 1976; Mar 19, 1976*
Sobel, Dr.: Mar 10, 1966*
Society for the Engouragement of Contemporary Arts: May 13, 1974
Society for Photographic Education: Apr 09, 1969
Solari, Paolo: see Photographs for gallery installations
Solem, Arnie: Jul 20, 1967
Sonnenburg: see Falkner von Sonnenburg, Erwin
Sonnenstahl, Bill: see Semanco, Al
Sonoma League for Historic Preservation: Dec 16, 1970
Sooy, Francis: see California: University of California at San Francisco
Southern Pacific Company: Dec 06, 1941; Dec 08, 1941*; Dec 23, 1941
Spear, Ann: Jul 27, 1957
Spencer, Paul: Aug 20, 1971
Spink & Gaborc, Inc.: Feb 12, 1965
Staempfli Gallery, Inc.: Jan 24, 1962
Stahlman, George: Oct 01, 1974; Oct 08, 1974*; Oct 19, 1974
Stammer, Ron: Jul 17, 1969*
Standard Pyroxoloid Corp.: Mar 12, 1969*; May 20, 1970*
Stanford University: Jan 23, 1967*; Feb 01, 1967; Feb 04, 1967; Feb 08, 1967; Feb 09, 1967; May 30, 1967*; Aug 20, 1969*; Sep 12, 1969; Jul 03, 1972; Jul 19, 1972*; Jul 27, 1972
State: U.S. Department of State: Jun 08, 1971; Jun 14, 1971*
Stauffacher, Jack Werner: Feb 17, 1965
Steichen, Edward: May 06, 1950*; May 22, 1950; Nov 17, 1959*; Jul 14, 1965; Jul 19, 1965*; Mar 17, 1969 (invitation)
Stein, B. F.: Jun 13, 1975*
Stein, Gertrude: see Metcalf: Addison M. Metcalf Collection of Gertrude Steiniana
Steinberg, Stefanie: Jan 07, 1973; Dec 25, 1973
Steinert, Otto: Dec 30, 1972*; mentioned in letter dated Jan 07, 1973 from Stafanie Steinberg; mentioned in letter dated Feb 01, 1974; Feb 07, 1974*; Feb 17, 1974*; Feb 28, 1974 (in German); Mar 01, 1974* (in German); Mar 25, 1974 (in German); Jun 03, 1974*
Stettner, Mr.: Jun 22, 1966*
Stewart, Mrs.: Jul 16, 1965*
Stieglitz: Alfred Stieglitz Archives, Yale University Library: Aug 30, 1961; Jan 08, 1962; Feb 03, 1962; Apr 09, 1962; Sep 26, 1962; Nov 29, 1962; Dec 21, 1962; Jan 16, 1963; also see Bunnell, Peter
Stieglitz, Jean (Alfred's niece): Feb 05, 1967; Feb 02, 1969; Feb 05, 1969*; Apr 19, 1969*; Apr 24, 1969; Apr 28, 1969*
Strand, Paul and Hazel: mentioned in [undated] letter from Cunningham to unidentified correspondent; Mar 18, 1960*; Mar 24, 1960; May 06, 1960; Jan 09, 1971*; Feb 23, 1971; Mar 26, 1971*; Jan 1973 (including photos of a house and 2 landscapes); Apr 14, 1973
Stratford, Hugh: Dec 19, 1966; Jan 06, 1967*
Straub, Bernice, and Maple Young: undated
Streeta, H. V. (Associated Press): Feb 04, 1967
Strother, John: Sep 23, 1971
Struss, Karl: Jan 25, 1919; Jan 1959; Jun 02, 1975; Jun 08, 1975*; Jun 21, 1975; Sep 15, 1975; Oct 11, 1975
Strybing Arboretum Society: Oct 28, 1976
Stuck, Mrs. Howard: Sep 06, 1964*
Sussman, Ross: see David: Peter M. David Gallery
Swift, Florence Alston: undated; [Oct 6], 1961; [Nov] 1, 1961
Tabler, Barbara: Oct 03, 1975
Tatlock, Hugh: Dec 20, 1964*; Jan 07, 1965; Apr 21, 1965*; Jan 19, 1967; Jul 31, 1967*; May 28, 1971; Jun 23, 1971*; Jan 12, 1972; Nov 08, 1972*; Nov 13, 1972
Taussig, Arthur: Jul 20, 1973; Oct 13, 1973; Oct 20, 1973*
Taylor, Adrian: Apr 07, 1972; Apr 12, 1972*
Teatro Municipale: Feb 10, 1983
TeeJay Publications: Oct 31, 1974; Nov 23, 1974*
Telford, John: see Edison Street Gallery